comed.com 2018-05-24

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
EFFECTIVE: August 18, 2017
Exelon Corporation (“Exelon”), its subsidiaries, including Atlantic City Electric Company
(“ACE”), Baltimore Gas and Electric Company (“BGE”), BGE Home Products & Services, LLC
(“BGE Home”), Commonwealth Edison Company (“ComEd”), Constellation NewEnergy, Inc.
(“Constellation”), Delmarva Power & Light Company (“DPL”), Exelon Generation Company,
LLC (“ExGen”), PECO Energy Company (“PECO”), Potomac Electric Power Company
(“Pepco”), and their respective subsidiaries (hereinafter referred to collectively as “Exelon
companies,” “us,” “we,” or “our”), are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of you,
our customers and the users of our websites and mobile applications (each, our “Site”) as
well as our products and services (“Services”). In light of this commitment, we adhere to
the practices provided below.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using our Site, you agree to our collection, use,
and sharing of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy.
From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy and will make reasonable efforts to
publish such changes. Any changes will be immediately effective upon the posting of the
updated Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Site represents your consent to the
terms of the new Privacy Policy. Please regularly check this Privacy Policy for any such
updates.
Collecting Personal Information
Through your use of our Site and Services we may collect Personal Information (“PI”),
which is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to you as an identifiable
individual. PI may include, but is not limited to, your first and last name, home or business
address, email address, and telephone number. We may also combine the PI that we collect
on our Site with information we collect about you offline.
We collect the following types of information:
       PI and Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) Provided by You
We collect PI from you when you use our Site and Services. While we do not require you to
provide PI in order to navigate our Site, we must collect certain PI and PII if you choose to
use our Services. PII includes information where your name is combined with your Social
Security number, driver’s license number, state identification card number, bank account
DMEAST #29926719 v1

number, credit card or debit card number, or unique biometric data. We may also collect PI
and PII when you create or modify an online account, complete any self-service transaction
with us online, or otherwise provide us with PI and PII in any correspondence. This may
include any of your questions, comments, or suggestions submitted through our Site or if
you fill out a survey.
When you voluntarily provide us with a cell phone number on our Site, you are giving us
express written consent to use that number for the purpose indicated, or if given with
regard to your utility account or other account with us, express written consent to
communicate information to you that is closely related to such account, so long as you have
not given us instructions to the contrary. You may revoke this consent at any time by any
reasonable method. Your consent to be contacted by us is not required in order to receive
our Services.
        Device and Usage Information
We may automatically collect the following types of information as you use our Site:
        •       Usage Information: We collect certain information automatically through
                your use of our Site, such as which pages on our Site you access, the
                frequency of access, purchases or other transactions made on our Site, and
                what you click on while on our Site.
        •       Location Information: We may collect information about your actual
                location that may be determined from GPS and other sensors that may reveal
                information on nearby devices, Wi-Fi access points, and cell towers.
        •       Device Information: We may collect information about the device you are
                using, such as hardware model, operating system, application version
                number, browser, and IP addresses.
        •       Mobile Device Information: In addition to the Device Information listed
                above, when you access our Site via a browser on your mobile device or
                through the use of one of our mobile applications, we may also collect mobile
                network information including telephone number, the unique device
                identifier assigned to that device, mobile carrier, operating system, and other
                device attributes. We may also access functions on your mobile device for the
                operation of our mobile application, which can include: telephone, camera,
                browser, social media apps, fingerprinting, or GPS.
                                                 2

        Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
“Cookies” are small text files that are stored within your computer’s or mobile device’s
memory by a website through your browser. Cookies enable a website such as ours to keep
track of your activities on that website, and to improve your use of the website, such as by
keeping track of your preferences.
You can change your browser settings on your personal computer or mobile device so that
cookies are not stored. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but you may not
have access to some of our Site’s functions and your ability to use some areas of our Site
may be limited.
We may also use other website or mobile tracking technologies to identify you and keep
track of your preferences, prevent fraudulent activity or improve Site security, assess the
performance of our Site, and deliver content to you based on your interests on our Site and
third-party websites.
        Aggregate Information
Statistical or aggregated information does not directly identify you or any specific person,
but it may be derived from your PI. For example, we may aggregate PI to calculate the
percentage of users in a particular ZIP code.
Third-Party Data Collection
Some content or applications accessible through our Site may be provided by third parties,
including analytics companies, payment processors, and advertising providers. Our Site
also includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button and other widgets,
such as the “Share” button or interactive mini-programs provided by third parties. These
third parties may use cookies or other tracking technologies to collect information about
you when you use our Site. The information they collect may be associated with your PI or
they may collect information, including PI, about your online activities over time and across
different websites and other online services.
We do not control the third-parties’ tracking technologies that are accessible through our
Site or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other
targeted content, you should read any privacy policy provided by the third-party website
or contact the responsible provider directly. Some of these third parties may provide you
with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used for targeted
advertising. For example, some of these third parties may be members of the Network
                                                3

Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), which provide a
single location where you can opt out of certain types of data collection or opt out of
receiving targeted ads from member companies. To opt out, please visit the NAI’s website
at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp or www.aboutads.info to
exercise choice with respect to participants of the DAA.
One third-party service we use is Google Analytics, which is a service provided by Google.
Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of our Site and may share
this data with other Google services. You can learn more about Google’s privacy practices
by visiting their website at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. We also
use the web customer satisfaction survey services of Foresee Results. You can learn more
about Foresee’s privacy practices by visiting their website at
http://www.foreseeresults.com/privacy-policy.shtml.
How We Use and Share Information
We use the PI we collect in the following ways:
        •      Communicate: We use PI to communicate with you about our Site or
               Services. We may also use your PI to send you account updates or other
               communications regarding your account or to inform you of any changes to
               our Site or Services, or to send you information, recommendations and
               promotions that we believe will be of interest to you. Exelon companies may
               send the contact information collected through our Site to other Exelon
               companies, to the extent permitted by applicable law, or such
               communications may be sent directly to you through our Site, such as push
               notifications.
               You should note that Exelon companies may use other electronic media for
               communications (such as social media), which may have their own separate
               privacy policies that govern the privacy of information that is shared or
               collected through your use of them.
        •      Specific Purposes: You may be asked to provide information for a specific
               purpose. We will only use that information for that purpose.
        •      Customer Support: We may use your PI to provide you support or other
               services you request. For example, we may need certain information in order
               to provide technical support or answer questions about our Site or Services.
                                                4

       •     To Improve Our Services: We may use your PI for statistical analyses,
             generating surveys, and doing market research in order to improve our
             Services. We may use information collected on our Site to personalize your
             experience on our Site.
       •     Site Maintenance: We analyze how our users interact with our Site in order
             to maintain and improve our Site. We also use information that we collect to
             diagnose any problems with our Site.
       •     Legitimate Business Purposes. We may use your PI or PII for any other
             business purpose we deem legitimate, as permitted by applicable law.
We reserve the right to share information, including PII, with third parties, as described
below:
       •     Service Providers: We may share information with service providers that
             help us perform Site functions and process your transactions. For example,
             we share information with electronic bill payment service providers so that
             you may pay for Services through our Site.
       •     Affiliates and Franchisees: We may share information with a parent
             company, franchisees, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under
             common control with us, to the extent permitted by applicable law.
       •     Corporate Structure: We may share information in connection with a
             merger, acquisition, consolidation, change of control, or sale of all or a
             portion of our assets or if we undergo bankruptcy or liquidation.
       •     To Prevent Harm: We may share information if we believe it is necessary in
             order to detect, investigate, prevent, or take action against illegal activities,
             fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the rights, property, or
             personal safety of any person.
       •     As Required by Law: We will share information where we are legally
             required to do so, such as in response to court orders or legal process, to
             exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims or demands, or to
             comply with the requirements of any mandatory applicable law.
       •     With Your Consent: We may request your permission to share your PI for a
             specific purpose. In such case, we will notify you and request consent before
                                              5

                you provide the PI or before the PI you have already provided is shared for
                such purpose.
Security
The security of your PI and PII is important to us. We maintain reasonable physical,
technical, and administrative security measures to protect and limit access to your PI and
PII. No method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage technology is 100%
secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your PI
and PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
You should exercise discretion in what information you send to us by email. We cannot
guarantee that email sent over the Internet is secure and will not be intercepted by others
before it reaches us. We are not responsible for the security of information contained in
emails sent over the Internet.
We will use reasonable efforts to maintain secure connections with you and limit access to
databases containing your PI and PII to authorized parties, including our own employees,
whose access to your information is on a need-to-know basis.
Applicable Law
This is a United States-based Site that is subject to U.S. law. If you are accessing our Site
from a location outside the U.S., you hereby agree that your use of our Site and our
collection and use of your PI and PII are subject to this Privacy Policy. When you submit PI
or PII to us, you are agreeing to permit us and our subsidiaries and affiliates to access,
store, and use the information wherever in the world we and our subsidiaries and affiliates
do business, both inside and outside the United States.
Children’s Privacy
Our Site is intended to provide general information about the Exelon companies and their
Services. We will not knowingly collect PI from children under 13 years of age, nor will we
knowingly allow children under 13 years of age to use certain features of our Site without
the consent of a child’s parent or guardian. We will not knowingly disclose PI collected
from children. If we become aware that a child under 13 years of age has provided us with
PI, we take immediate steps to delete such PI.
                                                6

External Links
In some cases, our Site links to other websites that collect PI and PII by and for other
parties. In these cases, the PI and PII you provide on those websites is governed by the
privacy policy of that website. We do not assume responsibility for the actions of other
parties.
Do Not Track
Our Site is not currently configured to respond to Do Not Track signals sent by browsers.
Disclosure to Government
We reserve the right to monitor and disclose, without your consent, any communications,
PI or PII, whenever requested to do so by courts, government agencies, or by law
enforcement authorities.
Contact Us
We will use reasonable efforts to address concerns you may have about this Privacy Policy
or your PI and PII. You may contact us by using the “Contact Us” area of our Site or sending
an email to WebAgent@exeloncorp.com.
                                               7
